Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you very much.
This is Ogisaka-chan from the end of the day!
Let's be friends today!
Let's go!
Listen to this.
What did you say?
Listen to me.
Come on, come on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Before this project, you gave us a presentation last time.
If Kubo had a bad drink, he wanted to have a long tea with us.
That's done!
In order to get a T-shirt with a picture of Bananaman at the reward meeting the other day
Kubo drank the punishment drink with a straight face
The long-awaited reward arrived today!
It was made to meet Kubo's request!
Seino
We're all the same!
I see... I'm glad!
I guess I'll go with "M" then, right?
I'd like to come with you, Mr. Himura... in a tight fit.
Don't be silly. Why do you call him Excel?
Excel is Mr. Himura?
But maybe you'd like a bigger girl.
I like big ones too.
Can I get one?
This much?
Dare I?
Yes, this one.
But, yeah, it's got an engine.
But maybe you want a bigger one.
But, you know, you don't know how big this Excel is until you put it together.
Yeah, it's pretty big.
Then why don't we look at it first?
Don't look at it yet, don't look at it yet, don't look at it yet.
Not yet.
Okay, which way?
Which way?
Boom!
Oh, my God!
Is that the back?
Yeah, it's my back.
I wanted to do your back.
That's good.
It's so good.
Oh, my God, with the backpack on, it's gonna be hidden.
Why is it hidden?
It's tiny, but...
But it fits in here?
You can't fit in this M.
I can fit in that kind of thing, even if it's just for a story.
You're 3 years old.
You want to wear your studio clothes.
I'm in.
Wow.
I'm sure you'll get in.
Not that much.
It's tiny.
The result won't be that interesting.
So, Nimura tried on the medium size
This is a medium.
And I don't have a T-shirt.
I want you to take off the T-shirt, too.
That's...
I want you to take it off.
Please don't.
Mr. Himura wants to see.
He wants to see you.
Everyone wants to see her undressed.
But you know, Mr. Himura used to say that if I wore loose-fitting clothes, I'd look too fat.
He said I should wear those tight ones, so I've been wearing them ever since.
There you go.
I'm scared.
What's so funny?
No, no, it's not that funny.
No, it's not that crazy.
Well, it's not like it's super tiny.
The problem with this is that if you do it like this, you'll never get it back.
If you say "yay", it's back.
Why do you say "yay"?
This is what I'm doing this summer.
It's hot.
Now then... please announce today's project, Mr. Himura.
There's someone I want to talk to you about.
Te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te te
No, not at the end.
This time, we've gathered a lot of talk topics that we all wanted to talk about after all this time.
Bananaman and the members will take the time to talk about them and bring everyone even closer together!
First of all, Shibata
Yes, sir.
You don't look familiar to me in that pose, do you?
Unfamiliar?
The beard and sunglasses are missing.
That's for sure.
Long time no see, Shibata.
Yes, it has.
It didn't suit you at all.
That's true.
What do you want to talk about?
I don't know.
I like fruit best among foods.
Fruit sounds good.
He brought us strawberries at the birthday concert.
He already had many kinds.
So I was wondering if you know of any other delicious varieties of fruit as well.
I see.
But the most advanced and maximal one right now is Amarin, the strawberry you had at that time.
Amarins were amazing, right?
They were so delicious!
I went to the fruit stand in Toyosu to get them.
Thank you very much!
Thank you, Mr. Yao, for coming nonstop.
Yes, there's a man named Mr. Yao who often comes nonstop, and I've become acquainted with him.
I've come to know him, so I'm ready for any kind of fruit.
Mr. Yao, you've been selling a lot of Amarin Amarins lately, too.
Amarin Amarin
Amarin Amarin.
You know...
I'd like to know if there's anything else.
You know what else is coming up this season? Elizabethan melons.
It's a yellow melon, cheap, but it's the kind of melon they sell, the old-fashioned kind.
I cut them into thin slices and eat them whole.
They're going out of season soon.
Why are you leaving?
Why is it coming out?
It's a melon!
Wow!
They look like oranges.
And now they're cut into pieces, but I would cut them into about three pieces.
And thin it out.
Thin it out.
Like Mr. Aken's.
Like Mr. Shimura's watermelon, but with melon marks.
I like this one because it's sweet and has just the right amount of firmness.
We also have grapes... the Shine Muscat, which has become popular, but if it's purple, it's the Nagano Purple.
I said Nagano.
Nagano purple is the best purple grape.
Everyone knows it.
And, what's that long, thin, Chichibu, where I'm from... a combination of long, thin, Shine Muscat and Nagano Purple.
It's like a combination.
It's really good, but I don't know what it's called.
It's coming up, so I'm kind of hoping for it.
You can buy them seedless, and they're super sweet.
Kubo's watermelon is good.
Yes, from Kobanazawa!
Obanazawa watermelon.
It's so good!
You know, the ones they make there?
You know the guy who makes them?
When he cuts them for shipment, if they're not good enough, he won't sell them.
But he's one of the best in Obanazawa.
There's a Kobanazawa within Kobanazawa.
The best of the best.
Mr. Yao.
From Mr. Yao.
Mr. Yao's top class. The guy in charge of fruit watermelons told me.
Heh.
That's right.
I don't mean to sound bashful, but if you watch Non-Stop, you'll know more about it.
There was a show called "Non-Stop Fruit Swamp".
Once.
What else?
The plum tree.
Plums!
Plums are gourmet, too.
I love peaches, too, but I forget where they're from, but they're called natsukko.
Natsukko!
They're huge!
One piece is...
But they're pink and I like them hard.
I like them hard, but they soften up when you put them down, and the Natsukko are so good!
Natsukko!
I think it's the snack pineapple from Miyako Island.
The kind you can rip off!
Delicious, delicious!
I love that delicious snack pineapple!
I usually say that in the supermarket, but it's an apple variety called "Akieiei".
Akiei
It's a variety called
Akiei.
Aki Ei Ei
It means that the season is changing to autumn.
Shifting.
Shift.
This one.
It doesn't look sour.
But it has just the right balance of sweet and sour.
And what's more...
The honey is amazing!
Sometimes apples are so disappointing, aren't they?
They have to stand on their own.
No, it's not like that. All the apples are crispy and crunchy, but the sweetness and tartness are just right.
but with just the right amount of sweetness and tartness.
The honey is amazing!
It's delicious!
We had apples too, right?
The honey is really bad.
The nectar that's already star-shaped.
Wasn't that delicious?
Delicious!
What was it?
I don't remember.
Maybe it was on the Internet... the Banana Man Space apple.
The one Orrin introduced me to.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Olin's coming out.
I've got the apple girl.
Olin came out... probably.
Commits.
Comitu.
Star-shaped honey.
I'm going like this... today.
It's fun.
It's fun. It's fun.
I wish I could have done it in pajamas or something.
Pajama talk.
Why pajama talk?
Let's go to the next talk.
Okuda.
Yes?
Actually, about 11 years ago...
About 11 years ago.
Yes.
I met Mr. Himura on the street
That's great.
I don't know...
I was walking near one of the studios
Mr. Himura got off the bus
carrying two lunch boxes.
He got off the bus.
What's with that?
Yes, me too.
I was with my mother.
I was with my mother
She said she wouldn't shake my hand.
I was shaking hands with Mr. Himura.
Salo, you remember shaking hands with him.
How are you shaking hands when you're holed up in your lunch box?
That's how it was.
If you'll excuse me.
Oh, my God.
Yes, sir. I can smell it.
After we shook hands?
It smelled so good.
I still remember it. It's amazing.
What's that? You mean the smell of my lunch box?
It's a good smell.
What kind of good smell?
Mr. Himura's.
I wore perfume back then.
That's how he smells.
Mr. Himura's.
If I say "Mr. Himura," it smells bad.
Remember?
I remember it.
I'm sure.
She'll remember.
You didn't take any pictures?
No, I didn't.
I wish we had. That would have been interesting.
Did you talk about anything else that happened?
Who was it?
Mr. Himura.
Do you remember meeting him on New Year's Day, 2015?
New Year's?
Malaysia.
Langkawi.
I went to Langkawi.
I used to go there all the time back then.
I did.
You went to Langkawi?
I went on a small plane with Mr. Himura, Mr. Kenkova and a junior comedian.
I heard there weren't that many people in a small plane.
Not that many.
Are they in the plane? There's a chrome.
Yes.
There's like 20 of them.
Is that so?
There were 20 of us, and we were all on the same plane to Langkawi with Kenkova.
All together.
Did you know it was Mr. Himura?
Yes, I did.
I understand.
When the junior comedians arrived at the airport, they wanted to take a picture.
Mr. Himura and the others were gathering, and I was trying to get in the back for a photo.
I was like, "Yay!
I don't know if I was in the picture, but I was like, "I'm sorry, Mom.
Heh.
I did it, didn't I?
That's my junior taking this picture.
That's right.
Wow.
So, if you look back at the pictures from back then, you see it?
That's what I'm talking about.
You're in the picture?
That's great.
Back then, you loved that side of the country... and Indonesia.
He had a wife there.
That's how much I love Indonesia.
Yes, yes, he and Kenkova go on a New Year's trip every year.
We've been doing it for about 15 years.
After all, they were talking about going to Lanka Way after work on live TV.
I happened to be watching it at home, and I thought it was the same place, and then I realized I was on a plane.
So it's a good fit.
Kimura-san, you're so perfect for each other!
They're perfect for each other.
About 10 years ago.
You know, we've been working with Nogizaka for years, but we've never seen each other on the street.
No.
But I always imagine them having dinner together.
I hate them.
You should pay them secretly.
That's disgusting.
That's the one.
I'd like to do the one I paid for on the sly.
We all do. - That's not why.
That's why we don't go to the same places, you know, like Denny's or something.
I don't think we'd see each other at a Denny's or something.
It's hard to pay for something at Denny's.
You know, you'd have the receipt.
Where are you going with this?
If they're eating and they say, "Oh, yeah, I'll pay for it.
I'd like to do that.
It's Mr. Kimura.
He'll be gone by then.
Shall we move on?
Okay.
I'll make snacks for when we drink at home.
You drink?
I can't say it out loud, but...
TV, TV, TV
Now that it's been on for about noon
I didn't have an image of it.
I'm sure you didn't.
He's only 18 years old, right?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Something to drink with.
I don't drink much, but there will be snacks.
Sake snacks.
Sake snacks
Yuzu cider... that's what I've been drinking.
No, no, no, no.
Yuzu cider
Eat at home or eat at a restaurant
No, I prefer home
Home.
What do you like, Kimura?
I really like 7-Eleven's boiled eggs.
Delicious!
I eat boiled eggs.
I like boiled eggs.
They leave about 5 boiled eggs.
Five.
It's not bad!
5 boiled eggs
It's Eiji Bando, isn't it?
Nobody is Eiji Bando, right?
Put down 5 boiled eggs.
Five boiled eggs!
That's an egg monster!
Amazing!
There must be a few drinkers here.
When I make snacks at home, I put shiso leaves with soy sauce, sesame oil, mirin, and a little bit of salt and pepper.
I put in some hawk's claws and that's it.
It's just like that.
It's so good!
Oba Daikon
I make it at home with shiso leaves, soy sauce, sesame oil, sugar and white soup stock.
Sesame oil, white soup stock, sugar, and so on.
Over-ripe daikon
It is delicious as it is or wrapped in seaweed.
How many cuts of it are you going to pick up?
And 7-Eleven's grilled tongue!
That's delicious!
It's delicious, isn't it?
Do you know it?
I've heard of it, but it's not famous.
No, it's still there.
Yes, there is.
I can't find it.
I can't find them.
Maybe I've had one of those... that Tuck's type.
This is really delicious!
It has a strong flavor, so it probably goes really well with alcohol.
I'm looking for this too!
This is really good!
I love sweets, too.
Sweets are good, too!
Sweets!
My golden pattern is to go for sweets, and my thirst goes on forever.
I've always loved dried scallops.
Sato Sui's dried scallops are outstandingly delicious.
That's right.
Sato Sui.
So when you go to Hokkaido, why don't you buy some of those since they're sold out on the mail order site?
Eh?
There's this snack Baby Star that I do.
The kind with peanuts.
It's a little spicy.
It's good.
Or you can make your own.
I don't drink that much, but I think it's a great snack.
It's called Tochio-age, which is a very thick fried tofu.
From Niigata.
You cut up an octopus, put natto (fermented soybeans) in it, put green onions on it, and serve it with soy sauce.
It's seared a little bit.
I eat it with ginger, and it's so good that you can eat it as a meal by itself.
It's good!
What do you eat, Endo?
I like sweets too, so the best sweets are Kaki no Tane!
I end up with kaki no tane.
And then there's a big version of Yotchan Ika, the kind with squid in it.
That's the dry food pattern, right?
Probably the same pattern.
I know what you mean.
Try boiled eggs. Seriously, just one or two.
I'll try it.
We don't talk about this stuff often.
Hey...
What's the best first song at a running karaoke bar?
I love karaoke and often go alone on my days off.
I often go to karaoke parties with people who have the day off alone, but I'm usually alone.
At those times, I can't sing out the first song, so I wonder who will go.
It depends on the members, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
There's a difference between a party and a party with friends.
Kubo, you know, if you sing the first song from Mugisaka, it's a big hit.
I don't sing group songs at karaoke anymore.
That's right.
Some of the members don't even sing together.
You're idols, right?
Mr. Iwasawa
Idols get excited when they sing idol songs.
And it's not like they raise it too high all at once.
That's right.
He's a muscle man.
Muscle man is call and response.
Running.
He says he's gonna fall down beautifully.
I don't feel like I'm singing with someone who says I'm going to fall down.
I never sing the first song that I want to sing the most.
On the contrary.
Well, I wouldn't go for the first song, would I?
It's not a throwaway song, but...
It's more like a throating.
Throating
When we sang the first song, right around the chorus, there was a cup of oolong tea that we had ordered.
I was like, "You're an idiot.
If it were me, for example...
Koji Tamaki, for example.
I'd save the ones I wanted to share with the audience, like Southern music.
And there's something else that's sure to get people excited.
Like Shonan no Kaze...
Oh, like watermelon...
Watermelon, that's a definite crowd pleaser.
That's a throw away song.
I don't give a shit.
It's not a throwaway song.
But I often go to karaoke with Yoshida and the others, and he always goes to the first song.
What? Yoshida, what are you going to sing?
I tend to sing my first song first.
That's cute.
A kiss?
It's okay, but it's okay.
What?
No, it's not.
While we were singing it, he said, "Well, you'll have to decide.
A ditched song.
It's a throwaway, and it's a gorgeous throwaway.
No, it's a song I like.
I put it in because I think it's cute and I want to sing it.
It's not the kind of song that gets people excited because no one sings it in the first song, but...
Then I say, "Let's put it in." I put it in.
Are there any members who say they'll sing the first song?
I'm going to sing the first song, too.
I'm going to sing the first song.
Okuda too?
Yes.
Who'll sing? Do you want to sing for them?
Not a member of Nogizaka, but a friend, like Garuru.
That's a good idea.
But it'll be fun.
People would love it.
And maybe some beetles.
Beetles?
That's great.
That's a great song.
I'd like to go when it's a little more exciting.
Let's save the beetles.
You're right.
It's always a little too quiet.
Yeah.
I'm a little worried, but no one's coming in, so...
I'll just say it out loud... it's cute.
Kakei.
If I were a member, I'd only go with Yuna.
She's a good singer, so I want to hear her sing that song.
I make a lot of requests.
If it's a member who's already decided, then we've already decided too.
We used to do this at the end of karaoke or at the end of a live show.
Then we would put in all the songs.
Yes, we would.
We'd make them sing.
Oh...
I know what I'm going to sing.
Almost.
Right.
This machine has been in front of him all this time.
I mean...
I'm almost the same.
Like this, from the skin.
It's going around like this.
Like this, like this, like this, like this.
And when it gets big, it starts singing.
Wow.
It's like that all the time.
It's like he sings when he comes in, even though he hasn't put it in.
I'll sing when they come in.
Why doesn't everyone put it in?
If you make a song like that, it'll sell.
It's called "Karaoke First Song".
Oh, wow!
That's a great idea!
Let's have fun today!
something like that.
Ah.
Like that.
First karaoke song.
If it's definitely the first song and everyone's in trouble...
You're right.
That's for sure.
You know...
Let's get over this stomach ache.
Nogizaka's strongest member item is decided
SakaguchiSakaguchi
Shitara-san gave me a space seal before.
The Universe Power Stickers from Uchu-mura.
He told me that there are yin and yang, and that if I put it on my body, my luck would go up.
If you put it on, your luck will go up from the smallest things.
I don't wear it now.
Why don't you wear it?
I don't know, but a lot of other members started wearing it.
It's all the rage now, so I'm keeping it.
I'm going to sell them in sheets for a very high price.
I'd like to know if there are any other good luck charms.
Good luck charms.
I mean, not spacey stuff.
I know that voice.
I know Kegonji Temple in Kyoto.
Suzumidera Temple.
I've been there.
It's really popular.
They have a monastery where you can listen to a monk for about 30 minutes.
I sometimes go to listen to them.
I love it, so I go there.
The good luck charms there are said to be very powerful.
Some kind of good luck charm.
I don't know if this has anything to do with good luck charms.
But there's a baseball team that I like.
I got the former manager's autograph.
He told me that if I put it in my bag, it would bring me good luck.
I put it in, and I got a job with the team.
But you said the manager was this kind of person, right?
That's Mr. Suji!
Oh...
You like "Save"?
I like Saves.
That's right. You like saves.
Suji is a great second baseman.
He's the best second baseman of our generation.
Then what's with the first pitch?
I'm going to throw out the first pitch for this season's Lions Night Game.
That's great!
Amazing!
I thought it was thanks to this.
Isn't that what he said?
You know that one? He's famous.
You know the one by Shunichi Kawai?
Did you know that if you take a picture of Shunichi Kawai and put it on your wallpaper, it'll boost your power?
I don't know.
But there are people like that sometimes.
I was just going into some details.
Akihiro Miwa.
Akihiro Miwa as a standby.
It was very popular when I was a student.
But, Shunichi Kawai... a lot of miraculous things have happened to him.
Shunichi Kawai?
The Shunichi Kawai era.
So many things happened.
That's why that era was so powerful.
I have to meet and photograph Shunichi Kawai.
Is it okay if it's an image of Shunichi Kawai?
I think it's okay.
I can't take a picture of Mr. Kawai.
And even if I met Shunichi Kawai...
I can't take a picture of his face.
You're too high up.
Mr. Kawai gets his picture taken a lot.
I'm writing this rumor.
He's a pain in the ass.
Someone's here.
Shun Takano...
Shun Takano's wallpaper cures my stomach ache.
Yay! I want it! I want it!
I have to have a picture of the city as my wallpaper?
Yay!
It's true.
Everyone knows that.
I have a stomach ache. It's going to get better.
Well, let's just go to Ise.
I want to go to Ise... with you guys.
I want to go, I want to go, I want to go
I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
That's why when we're talking like this...
You thought I was lying.
The high has stopped.
You're making too much noise.
Did you just take that?
I don't know what's gotten into me.
I really am.
Oh, my God!
Maybe I'm possessed.
It was this big, right?
Even if it was, you wouldn't have done it on M-Station or something.
If it was on Kohaku, I wouldn't do it.
Really?
It's not that great.
Oh, my God!
My eyes flew open.
That's because...
It's because you're athletic.
My body's moving.
Oh, my God.
That's amazing.
Tickets for Mizuki Yamashita's graduation concert
Tickets are now on sale.
Hello.
This is Iyoki Mao.
For tomorrow's lunch, everyone.
Tomorrow, please have rice topped with cod roe.
I want some of that.
I'll have it.
Please subscribe and rate my channel!
Bye bye!